Guide to the Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records, 1922-1979, 1922-1958 (bulk)
Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Forest Hills Gardens Corporation records, 1922-1979 1922-1958
2775
Forest Hills Gardens Corporation (Forest Hills, New York, N.Y.)
29.4 cubic ft., 1 reel positive, 2 reels negative microfilm.
Correspondence, minutes, reports, memoranda, vouchers, orders, notices, clippings, specifications, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes materials relating to the history of Forest Hills Gardens, a planned residential community in Queens, New York that was devleloped by the Russel Sage Foundation in 1908.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Forest Hills Gardens is a planned residential community which was developed by the Russell Sage Foundation in 1908. Laid out on 175 acres in Queens, New York, the community's site plan was designed by Frederick Law Olmsted; many of the houses were designed by Grosvenor Atterbury.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes correspondence, minutes, reports, memoranda, vouchers, orders, notices, clippings, specifications, and other materials pertaining to Forest Hills Gardens meetings, committees, director, constitution and by-laws, insurance and liability, finance, maintenance, development, construction, zoning, maintaining architectural standards and aesthetic control, building restrictions and waivers, streets and parking, complaints, policies, the sale of property to "undesirables," the Ives-Quinn anti-discrimination bill, and other subjects. Also included are reports of the Architectural Committee and correspondence with the Russell Sage Foundation, the Sage Foundation Homes Co., Forest Hills Dwellings, Inc., residents, and the New York City Planning Commission.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Forest Hills Gardens Corporation (Forest Hills, New York, N.Y.); Forest Hills Dwellings.; Forest Hills Gardens Corporation. Architectural Committee.; New York (N.Y.). City Planning Commission.; Russell Sage Foundation.; Sage Foundation Homes Company.
Subjects:
City planning--New York (N.Y.); Community development, Urban.; Discrimination in housing.; Urban transportation.; Zoning.
Places:
Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.)--Buildings.; Queens County (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Specifications.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Corporate minutes: access restricted to permission of donor.
Available Copies:
Corporate minutes, 1922-1958 are on microfilm. Originals retained by donor.
RELATED MATERIAL
See also Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.) Records, ( #2495).
Development of the Vanderveer Tract
Materials in Box 28, where noted, pertain to the development of the Vanderveer Tract, which adjoins Forest Hills Gardens and over which FHG has architectural control as per agreement of May 17, 1923
SERIES LIST
Series I. Alphabetical Files and Other Correspondence
1921-1922
1923-1929
1930-1934
1935-1939
1940-1944
1945-1950
Miscellaneous
Vanderveer Tract
Block 12
Series II. Vouchers, Permits, and Legal Documents
Vouchers
Permits
Legal Documents
Series III. Maps, Plans, Oversized Items, Brochures, and Glass Plate Negatives
Maps, Plans, Oversized Items
Brochures
Glass Plate Negatives
CONTAINER LIST
- Alphabetical Files
  Arranged Chronologically
  - 1916-1922
    - Men's Club of Forest Hills, 1921-1922 (Box 20)
      Lists and correspondence
    - Atterbury, 1922 (Box 20)
      Letter to Forest Hills Garden Corp. regarding suggestions in matters of "Aesthetic Control" (4 pages)
    - Organization of Gardens Corp., 1922 (Box 20?)
      Correspondence regarding transferral of rights and obligations from the Homes Company to an as yet unnamed Corporation; copy of Roland Park (Baltimore, MD) Corporation Papers
  - 1923-1930
    - 1923
      - A and B - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
        Especially Atterbury
      - C - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - D - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
        Men's Club lists and correspondence; additionally, excerpts from FHG Bulletin 1915-1923 (four typed pages) and 1928 correspondence especially regarding Block 12 controversy (apt. house)
      - D - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - E - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - F - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - Forest Hills Gardens Bulletins - including Christmas Number December 13, 1924, 1923-1924 (Box 27)
      - G - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - H - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - I - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - Insurance, 1923-1925 (Box 20)
        Regarding politics
      - J - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - K - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - L - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - M - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - N - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - Olmstead Brothers, 1923 (Box 20)
        Letter from Olmstead Brothers (landscape architects) acknowledging receipt of Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws of Gardens Corp. (1 page)
      - P - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - Q - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 1)
      - R - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - S - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - Speir (a director) - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 1)
      - T - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
      - W - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20)
    - 1924
      - A - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
        Atterbury letter regarding architectural supervision
      - Adsit Reports - Office diary by Mrs. Adsit, May 1924 (Box 7)
      - B - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
      - C - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
      - D - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
      - H - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
      - M - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
        Includes newspaper clippings regarding barring of 2 family homes in Union Turnpike (by Bloodgood)
      - N - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
        Especially with Newton Gas Co. regarding permission to open streets at various locations
      - O - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1)
      - Orders - FHGC office orders especially addressograph plates (Box 1)
      - P - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1)
      - Printing, 1924 (Box 20)
        Includes copies of printed notices sent to lot owners contemplating building regarding restrictions
      - S - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 20)
      - Streets, 1923-1924 (Box 20)
        Memo affecting Union Turnpike frontage (2 pages)
      - W - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1)
    - 1925
      - A - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
        Between "A" property owners and FHGC regarding development and maintenance
      - B - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
        Includes a letter from DWSG & E regarding lighting of private streets (city does not supply); correspondence regarding development of P.S. 101
      - Judge Boyce - list of delinquent maintenance, 1925 (Box 1)
      - C - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
        Correspondence between Cord Meyer Development Co. and FHGC regarding Sewer Pumping Station; misc. "C" correspondence especially Chatford Homes Development Corp.
      - D - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
        Includes copy of proposed agreement (unsigned) between FHGC and Forest Hills Dwellings, Inc. regarding wavier to permit houses to stand closer to street (95 houses on Burns St.)
      - E - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
        Between "E" property owners and FHGC regarding development and maintenance
      - Four Mill Maintenance Agreement, June 26, 1924 (Box 1)
        Report of "Four Mill Committee" to FHGC - read and approved and adopted at directors meeting July 3, 1924, (members to pay Four mills tax for maintenance and nothing for dues) - agreement to run with the land (formerly agreement was 2 mills tax, 2 mills membership dues); also copy of earlier Four Mill Agreement dated October 1, 1923, (raising from 2 mills the assignment from the Homes Company)
      - G - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
      - Gardens Corp. Bulletin, 1925 (Box 1)
      - H - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
      - I - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
      - J - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
      - K - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
      - L - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
      - Lamp Posts, 1923-1925 (Box 1)
        Correspondence regarding damages and repairs
      - M - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
        Includes correspondence regarding "Eagle" (Safety) Patrol
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
      - Minutes FHGC Members Meetings, 1923-1925 (Box 1)
        Minutes of directors' and open meetings
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 1)
        Regarding development and maintenance charges between property owners and FHGC; letter from NYC Fire Dept. denying request for fire alarm system, (i.e. boxes in our streets)
      - N - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
      - Newton Register Printing - Correspondence with printing company (Box 1)
      - Parks, 1923-1925 (Box 1)
        Reports on private lanes, private parks, Olivia and Hawthorne Parks, underground improvements, especially regarding taxes and maintenance
      - Publicity - Newspaper clippings, FH Bulletin, 1925 (Box 1)
      - Printing (Box 1)
        Proof copies of printing jobs, e.g.: FH Bulletin, copy of assessment agreement regarding 4 mill maintenance
      - R - Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 29)
        Mostly in architectural matters
      - S - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
        Includes Sprunk vs. FHGC regarding unauthorized building
      - Stowe, Lyman Beecher (director) - Correspondence (Box 1)
      - T - Correspondence, 1923 -1925 (Box 1)
        Includes Real Estate Tax levies for 1923 and other tax matters
      - Treasurers Reports, 1923-1925 (Box 1)
      - U - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
      - Utility Invoices, 1924-1925 (Box 27)
        Electric (for installations and current for particular lamps in FHG, numbering 1 to 4 locations) and telephone
      - V - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
    - 1926
      - A - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Atterbury Reports, 1926 (Box 27)
      - B - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - C - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Committee Reports, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Community Council A-G - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
        1923-1924, including copy of History and Constitution
      - Community Council J-S - Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 27)
      - D - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - E - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - F - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Forest Hills Flower Shop, 1926 (Box 27)
        Bills and receipts (inc. some 1923-1925 )
      - G - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
        Includes Laura Green Vouchers
      - Gardens Casino (proposed), 1926 (Box 27)
      - H - correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
        Includes copy of Four-Mill Agreement dated Oct. 1, 1923
      - I, J,& K - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - L - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
        Including one Atterbury letter
      - M & Mc - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Men's Club, 1925-1926 (Box 27)
      - N - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
        Including Electric Service Agreement for 8 Mazda Type lamps in FHG - also permits for installation of these
      - O & P - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Orders & Receipts, 1926 (Box 27)
      - R - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - S - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - T, U, & V - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1926 (Box 27)
        Includes trial balance
      - W & XYZ - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27)
    - 1927
      - A - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Atterbury Construction Reports, 1927 (Box 24)
        Memoranda on various homes under construction
      - B - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
        Includes Bulletin of Burns St. Association
      - Bulletin, 1926 (Box 24)
        Draft copies
      - C - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - D - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - E - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - F - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - G - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - H - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Dr. Hume (Director), 1924-1927 (Box 24)
      - I - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - J - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - K - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - L - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Lampposts, 1927 (Box 24)
        Regarding Gardens Corp. vs. Durlewanger-Koedenberg (accident)
      - M - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - N - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - O - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Orders, 1927 (Box 24)
      - P - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Printing, 1927 (Box 24)
        Proofs for notices prepared by printer
      - R - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - S - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - T - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1927 (Box 24)
        Monthly reports
      - V - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - W - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1927 (Box 24)
        Agreements with various homeowners
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 24)
    - 1928
      - A - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
        Includes some Atterbury letters
      - Atterbury Reports, 1928 (Box 18)
      - B - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Board of Estimates Petition (Legal Size Folder), 1928 (Box 18)
        Petition to Board of Estimates and Apportionment, City of NY for Zoning Change of Certain Property in FHG
      - C & D - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - E & F - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Four-Mill Agreements, 1928 (Box 18)
      - G - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - H - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - I & J - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Insurance, 1928 (Box 18)
      - K & L - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Lampposts, 1928 (Box 18)
      - M, Mc, & N - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - O & P - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Orders, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Publicity Committee, 1928 (Box 18)
        Includes newspaper clippings
      - Rhodes Reports, June 1928 (Box 18)
        Daily office log for this month (FHGC)
      - S - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - T - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1928 (Box 18)
      - U - Correspondence and Upkeep Committee Reports, 1928 (Box 18)
      - V - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 18)
    - 1929
      - A & B - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Atterbury Reports, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Boundary Markers, 1929 (Box 17)
        Also Atterbury blueprint for Groton St./Continental Ave. marker
      - Judge Boyce, 1927-1929 (Box 17)
      - C - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Committee Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 17)
      - Committee House, 1927-1930 (Box 17)
      - D - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - E - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Four-Mill Agreements, 1929 (Box 17)
      - G & H - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - I & J - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Insurance, 1929 (Box 17)
      - K - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - L - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Lampposts, 1929 (Box 17)
        Regarding lampposts and street signs
      - M & Mc - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - N - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - O & P - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Publicity Committee, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Q - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - R - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - S - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - T - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Teague (Chairman of Architectural Committee), 1926-1930 (Box 17)
      - Treasurers Report, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Trial Balance, 1929 (Box 17)
      - Upkeep Committees Report, 1929 (Box 17)
      - V & W - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 17)
  - 1930-1934
    - 1930
      - A & B - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Atterbury Reports, 1930 (Box 10)
        Reports on construction for various owners
      - Atterbury Reports, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Annual Meeting Program, May 13, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Architectural Submissions - Pending or approved (blue form), 1926-1930 (Box 15)
      - Judge Boyce, 1927-1930 (Box 15)
      - C - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Committee Reports, 1930 (Box 15)
        Minutes of Directors' Meetings and Annual Committee Reports, Minutes of Annual Meeting
      - D - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Judge Davies, 1930 (Box 15)
      - E - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - F & G - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - H - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Hanavan (Treasurer and Chairman of Law Committee), 1927-1930 (Box 15)
      - I - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Insurance, 1930 (Box 15)
      - J & L - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - K - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
        especially Kresse-Atterbury also contains the prospectus for The Greenway)
      - Lampposts and street signs, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Law Committee, 1930 (Box 15)
        Newspaper clippings regarding proposed By-Laws amendment increasing dues and approval of new purchasers (Forest Hills - Kew Gardens Post)
      - M & Mc - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - N - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Newspaper Clippings (Box 15)
        Regarding origins of FHG, "Block 12" dispute with Hariss (Leslie, apartment site), and Resolution to restrict membership (passed)
      - Orders, 1930 (Box 15)
      - P - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Q - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - R - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - S - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Sanitarium, 1930 (Box 10)
        Correspondence and legal matters concerning use of 392/394 Burns Street as a "Sanitarium"
      - Mr. Speir, 1926-1930 (Box 15)
      - Mr. Stowe - President FHGC ( 1926-1930 ), 1930 (Box 15)
      - T - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Taxicab Matters, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Treasurers Reports, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Trial Balance, 1930 (Box 15)
      - Traffic, 1930 (Box 15)
        Correspondence 1928 and 1929, regarding lights, signals (nothing from city)
      - U - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 10)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1930 (Box 10)
        Reports, estimates, costs, correspondence
      - V - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 10)
      - W - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 10)
      - Wilson, E.B. (Director) Correspondence, 1927-1930 (Box 10)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 10)
    - 1931
      - A - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - Atterbury, 1931 (Box 2)
        Reports on General Construction by Grosvenor Atterbury, Supervising Architect
      - B - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - Judge Boyce Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - C - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - Committee Reports - 1931 (Box 2)
        Treasurers reports, upkeep, finance, architecture, Board meetings, annual meetings
      - D - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - E - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - F - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
        Includes correspondence regarding easement of installation of Fire Alarm boxes in Gardens
      - Forest Arms Apartment Blueprint and letter of appreciation dated June 2, 1931, 1931 (Box 2)
        (folder mislabelled as "deposits")
      - Forest Arms, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Forest Hills Inn Apartment, 1931 (Box 25)
        (2 folders) year of construction
      - Four Mill Agreements, 1931 (Box 2)
        Lists of signers and copies of "member's assent to agreements"
      - G - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - H - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - I - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Insurance, 1931 (Box 25)
      - J - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - K - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - L - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Lampposts, 1931 (Box 25)
        Miscellaneous correspondence regarding broken lampposts, replacements
      - M - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - N - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - O - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Orders and Invoices, 1931 (Box 25)
      - P - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Publicity Committee, 1931 (Box 25)
        Drafts of newsletter and some newspaper clippings
      - Q - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - R - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - S - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Special Committee on Payment of Dues - - Reports on Arrears, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Specifications, 1931 (Box 25)
        For all buildings to be erected in FHG (additional), undated also additional Vanderveer specs, undated
      - T - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
        Especially with Walter Teague (Director), tax assessments on parks, sewers, private walks and lanes
      - Taxicab Matters, 1931 (Box 25)
        Includes materials on FH Taxi Association booth rental
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1931 (Box 25)
        Bookkeeping, reports, audits, inventories
      - Trial Balances, 1931 (Box 25)
        Ledger sheets and audits (8 copies)
      - U - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1931 (Box 25)
        Reports, inventory
      - V - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25)
      - W - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2)
    - 1932
      - A - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Arrears, 1932 (Box 11)
      - B - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 10)
      - Judge Boyce, 1932 (Box 10)
      - C - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 10)
      - Committee Reports, 1932 (Box 11)
        Reports and minutes of Committees and Annual Meetings
      - D - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - E - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Earle Wall (Box 11)
        Correspondence and matters relating to 399 Greenway Terrace; development of house and wall on Earle property - includes photos
      - F - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Four Mill Agreements, 1932 (Box 11)
        Regarding increase in assessment
      - G - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - H - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Insurance, 1932 (Box 11)
        Claims, correspondence
      - J - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - K - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - L - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Lampposts, 1932 (Box 11)
        Correspondence regarding suit and settlement regarding damaged lamppost
      - M - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
        Includes correspondence regarding mosquito control
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Mr. Mcmillin (Director), 1932 (Box 11)
      - N - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1932 (Box 11)
      - O - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Orders, 1932 (Box 11)
        Catalogs, receipts
      - P - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Publicity Committee, 1932 (Box 11)
        News items for Men's Club, some newspaper clippings
      - Q - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - R - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - S - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Speir (Director), 1931 (Box 11)
        mostly upkeep (2 folders)
      - Streets, 1932 (Box 11)
        Widening of Union Turnpike
      - Treasurers Reports, 1932 (Box 11)
        Accounts, reports, financial statements
      - Trial Balance, 1932 (Box 11)
        Work sheets for Treasurers Reports
      - Union Turnpike, 1932 (Box 11)
        Widening of Union Turnpike and connection to Interboro Parkway and Grand Central Parkway
      - Upkeep Committee, 1932 (Box 11)
        Time sheets, reports, and correspondence
      - V - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
      - W - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 11)
    - 1933
      - A - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Atterbury Reports, 1933 (Box 31)
        Correspondence and only one brief report
      - B - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Judge Boyce (Director), 1933-1934 (Box 31)
      - C - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)